Guide to the George W. Wilbur Family Papers
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
- George W. Wilbur's Personal and Business Papers, 1867-1931; Series III; 6.7; (17 boxes)
  - BUSINESS RECORDS
    - Milling and Mining
      - Bills and receipts, 1893-96 (Box 92, Folder 1579)
      - Bills and receipts (Box 92, Folder 1580)
      - Checks (canceled), 1891 Aug-Sep (Box 92, Folder 1581)
      - Contracts and deeds, 1887-1900, n.d. (Box 92, Folder 1582)
        See also: Oversize, Box 112, folder 1850
      - Correspondence, 1885-87 (Box 92, Folder 1583)
      - Correspondence, 1888 (Box 92, Folder 1584)
      - Correspondence, 1890 (Box 92, Folder 1585-1586)
      - Correspondence, 1891 (Box 92, Folder 1587-1593)
      - Correspondence, 1892 (Box 93, Folder 1594)
      - Correspondence, 1894 (Box 93, Folder 1595)
      - Correspondence, 1896 (Box 93, Folder 1596)
        See also: Oversize, Box 112, folder 1851
      - Correspondence, 1897 (Box 93, Folder 1597-1599)
      - Correspondence, 1898 (Box 93, Folder 1600-1604)
      - Correspondence, 1899 (Box 93, Folder 1605-1606)
      - Correspondence, 1900 (Box 93, Folder 1607-1608)
      - Correspondence, 1901 (Box 93, Folder 1609-1610)
      - Correspondence, 1904 (Box 93, Folder 1611)
      - Correspondence (Box 93, Folder 1612)
      - Correspondence both to and from others, 1889 (Box 93, Folder 1613-1614)
      - Correspondence both to and from others, 1890-92 (Box 93, Folder 1615)
      - Diary and expense book, 1889, 1891 (Box 93, Folder 1616)
      - Diary and expense book, 1890 (Box 93, Folder 1617)
      - Documents, 1889-93 (Box 93, Folder 1618)
      - Documents, 1896, n.d. (Box 93, Folder 1619)
      - Expense book, trip to Crested Butte, 1896 Jul-Aug (Box 93, Folder 1620)
      - Map of unidentified mine, n.d.
        See: Oversize, folder 1882
      - Maps of "Mammoth" mine, San Luis Obispo County, California, n.d.
        See: Oversize, Box 112, folder 1852, and Box 113, folder 1869
      - Hawkeye Consolidated Mining and Milling Company. Chicago: Rand, McNally and Company, Printers, 1882 (Box 94, Folder 1621)
      - Newspaper articles, 1886-1901 (Box 94, Folder 1622)
      - Placer mines in Idaho, 1894-95, n.d. (Box 94, Folder 1623)
      - Report on bituminous rock property in San Luis Obispo County, California, n.d. (Box 94, Folder 1624)
      - Fragments, n.d. (Box 94, Folder 1625)
    - Other Business Papers
      - W. G. Leonard in account with George W. Wilbur, 1873 (Box 94, Folder 1626)
  - WRITINGS
    - "Eminent Domain." Graduation speech at Union College of Law, [1870] (Box 94, Folder 1626a)
    - "Man" speech, n.d. (Box 94, Folder 1627)
    - "My Christmas Eve", 1875 Dec (Box 94, Folder 1628)
    - Articles and short stories, untitled (Box 94, Folder 1629)
    - Miscellaneous notes and notebook, 1873-75, n.d. (Box 94, Folder 1630)
  - OTHER PAPERS
    - Address book, n.d. (Box 94, Folder 1631)
    - Clippings, 1876 (Box 94, Folder 1632)
    - Documents: certificates, diplomas, licenses, 1870-1907 (Box 94, Folder 1633)
      See also: Oversize, Box 112, folders 1853-1856
    - Membership cards, 1875-1930, n.d. (Box 94, Folder 1634)
    - Name roster of tour group to Yellowstone and Rocky Mountain National Parks, [1925] (Box 94, Folder 1634a)
      Accompanied by stationery for Union Pacific System, West Yellowstone, Montana
    - Programs and handbooks, 1873-74 (Box 94, Folder 1635)
    - Secretary's Book, America Base Ball Club, 1867 (Box 94, Folder 1636)
    - Wallet notebook, 1868-72, n.d. (Box 94, Folder 1637)
      With George Wilbur's name in the front, mostly blank with writing in back that is not his
    - Will, typescript copy, n.d. (Box 94, Folder 1637a)
- Other Family Papers, 1737-1951; Series IV; 5.8; (14 boxes)
  Series IV, Other Family Papers, is organized into seven subseries: Cook and Rice Family Papers, Sarah Ann Cook Wilbur, Ellen Rice Wilbur, Albert H. Wilbur, Susan W. Rice, Susan Wilbur Jones, and Unidentified. Material in each subseries is arranged by format or by type of documentation.
  - COOK AND RICE FAMILY PAPERS
    - Cook Family
      - Documents, 1737-1861, n.d. (Box 95, Folder 1638)
      - Writings, 1825, n.d. (Box 95, Folder 1639)
      - Newspaper clipping, 1902 (Box 95, Folder 1640)
    - Rice Family
      - Flagg/Rice family documents: quit claims, discharge of debt, etc., 1828-45, n.d. (Box 95, Folder 1641)
      - Research notes on Stephen Flagg, n.d. (Box 95, Folder 1642)
        Includes notes written on the back of an official ballot for the Massachusetts state election for 1907
      - Rice, Francis H. and George H.
        See also: Charlotte and Francis H. Rice under Cases: Long Term Individual Client Files, folders 750-770
        - Account book, 1856-60 (Box 95, Folder 1643)
        - Account book, 1858-59 (Box 95, Folder 1644)
          Cover reads: "Fuller, Lawrence & Woods in account with F. H. Rice"
        - Account book, 1875-88 (Box 95, Folder 1645)
        - Account book, n.d. (Box 95, Folder 1646)
          Several different kinds of entries: list of Belvidere men's names with F. H. Rice's name among them, list of books, grocery lists, miscellaneous notes
        - Bills, receipts, promissory notes, 1838-46 (Box 95, Folder 1647)
        - Bills, receipts, promissory notes, 1855 (Box 95, Folder 1648)
        - Bills, receipts, promissory notes, 1856 (Box 95, Folder 1649-1650)
        - Bills, receipts, promissory notes, 1857 (Box 95, Folder 1651-1652)
        - Bills, receipts, promissory notes, 1858 (Box 95, Folder 1653-1654)
        - Bills, receipts, promissory notes, 1859 (Box 96, Folder 1655-1659)
        - Bills, receipts, promissory notes, 1860-69 (Box 96, Folder 1660)
        - Bills, receipts, promissory notes, n.d. (Box 96, Folder 1661-1662)
        - Correspondence, 1855-56 (Box 96, Folder 1663-1664)
        - Correspondence, 1857 (Box 96, Folder 1665-1666)
        - Correspondence, 1858 (Box 96, Folder 1667-1669)
        - Correspondence, 1859 (Box 96, Folder 1670-1671)
        - Correspondence, 1860-78 (Box 96, Folder 1672)
        - Correspondence (Box 96, Folder 1673)
        - Documents: Quit claim, discharge of debt, etc., 1847-62 (Box 96, Folder 1674)
          See also: Oversize, Box 112, folders 1857-1858
      - Rice, Susan C. and Mary C.
        - Bills and receipts, 1861-70 (Box 96, Folder 1675)
        - Bills and receipts, 1873-84 (Box 96, Folder 1676)
        - Bills and receipts, 1885-93, n.d. (Box 96, Folder 1676a)
        - Writings, n.d. (Box 96, Folder 1677)
      - Newspaper clippings about Rice relatives, 1899, n.d. (Box 96, Folder 1678)
  - WILBUR, SARAH ANN COOK
    - Financial Papers
      - Account book, 1851-72 (Box 97, Folder 1679-1680)
        One volume plus loose pages. Accounts for painting and wallpapering business run by George Wilbur, Senior (d. 1858) in front, with later entries in back of Sarah Ann Cook Wilbur's millinery business
      - Account book for millinery business, 1865-74 (Box 97, Folder 1681-1682)
        One volume plus loose pages. Accounts written in both Sarah Ann Cook and George Wilbur's hand. With a few scattered pages of household expenses
      - Account book (renters), 1891-94 (Box 97, Folder 1683)
      - Bills, receipts and documents, 1853-1901, n.d. (Box 97, Folder 1684)
        Includes three made out to George Wilbur (father)
    - Other Papers
      - Business Correspondence (incoming), 1874-1904 (Box 97, Folder 1685)
      - New Testament signed in front, "S.A. Cook", 1835 (Box 97, Folder 1686)
  - WILBUR, ELLEN RICE
    - Oak Park/Belvidere Property
      - Account book, n.d. (Box 97, Folder 1687)
      - Bills and receipts, 1892-99 (Box 97, Folder 1688)
      - Bills and receipts, 1900-03 (Box 97, Folder 1689)
      - Bills and receipts, 1904-05 (Box 97, Folder 1690)
      - Bills and receipts, 1906-07 (Box 97, Folder 1691)
      - Bills and receipts, 1908-27 (Box 97, Folder 1692)
      - Correspondence, 1895 (Box 97, Folder 1693)
      - Correspondence, 1896 (Box 97, Folder 1694)
      - Correspondence, 1897 (Box 97, Folder 1695)
      - Correspondence, 1898 (Box 97, Folder 1696)
      - Correspondence, 1899 (Box 97, Folder 1697)
      - Correspondence, 1904 (Box 97, Folder 1698)
      - Correspondence, 1905 (Box 97, Folder 1699)
      - Correspondence, 1906 (Box 97, Folder 1700)
      - Correspondence, 1907-08 (Box 98, Folder 1701)
      - Correspondence, 1909 (Box 98, Folder 1702)
      - Correspondence, 1910 (Box 98, Folder 1703)
      - Correspondence, 1911 (Box 98, Folder 1704-1706)
      - Correspondence, 1912 (Box 98, Folder 1707)
      - Correspondence (Box 98, Folder 1708)
    - Other Personal Business Correspondence
      - Correspondence, 1899-1911 (Box 98, Folder 1709)
      - Correspondence, 1912-15 (Box 98, Folder 1710)
      - Correspondence, 1916-19 (Box 98, Folder 1710a)
      - Correspondence, 1922-28 (Box 98, Folder 1710b)
      - Correspondence regarding 1916 Rockford College reunion, 1915 (Box 98, Folder 1711)
      - Correspondence regarding 1916 Rockford College reunion (Box 98, Folder 1712-1713)
    - Other Papers
      - Account book, Oak Park State Bank, 1899-1912 (Box 98, Folder 1714)
      - Bills and receipts, 1868-72 (Box 98, Folder 1715)
        Ellen's bills and receipts after her marriage in 1888 for everything except the Oak Park property are filed under George W. Wilbur's bills and receipts, series II, folders 1378-1417
      - Checks (canceled), 1909-15 (Box 98, Folder 1716)
      - Check registers, 1911-13 (Box 98, Folder 1717)
      - Notebook with partial diary, school notes, and poetry, 1870-71, n.d. (Box 98, Folder 1717a)
      - Miscellaneous poetry accompanying notebook with partial diary, school notes, and poetry (Box 98, Folder 1717b)
      - Writings (includes speech notes), n.d. (Box 98a, Folder 1718)
    - Printed Material
      - Newspaper articles from society page and about Carnegie library, 1909-11, n.d. (Box 98a, Folder 1719)
      - French grammar signed in front, "Nellie G. Rice", n.d. (Box 98a, Folder 1720)
      - Rockford Alumna Rockford College, 1932 Jan
        See: Oversize, Box 112, folder 1859
      - Woman's Society pamphlets, 1905-24 (Box 98a, Folder 1721)
      - Miscellaneous printed material, 1872-1914 (Box 99, Folder 1722)
      - Miscellaneous printed material, 1915-32, n.d. (Box 99, Folder 1723)
  - WILBUR, ALBERT H.
    - Checks (canceled), 1874-75 (Box 99, Folder 1724)
    - Business correspondence, 1884-90 (Box 99, Folder 1725)
    - Newspaper articles about Albert H. Wilbur's wedding, 1891 (Box 99, Folder 1726)
    - Report card, 1868 Feb 28 (Box 99, Folder 1727)
  - RICE, SUSAN W.
    - Bills and receipts, 1868-91 (Box 99, Folder 1727a)
    - Receipts from S.D. Warren and Co., 1910-17 (Box 99, Folder 1727b)
    - Writings, n.d. (Box 99, Folder 1727c)
  - JONES, SUSAN WILBUR
    - Personal Business Correspondence
      - Correspondence, 1907-33 (Box 99, Folder 1728)
      - Correspondence, 1935 (Box 99, Folder 1729)
      - Correspondence, 1936 (Box 99, Folder 1730)
      - Correspondence, 1937-38 (Box 99, Folder 1731)
      - Correspondence, 1939 (Box 99, Folder 1732)
      - Correspondence, 1940 (Box 99, Folder 1733)
      - Correspondence, 1941-42 (Box 99, Folder 1734)
      - Correspondence, 1943-45 (Box 99, Folder 1735)
      - Correspondence, 1946 (Box 99, Folder 1736)
      - Correspondence (Box 99, Folder 1737)
    - Financial Papers
      - Bills and receipts, 1910-42 (Box 99, Folder 1738)
        See also: Oversize, Box 112, folder 1860
      - Bills and receipts, 1943-51 (Box 99, Folder 1739)
      - Bills and receipts (Box 99, Folder 1740)
      - Checks (canceled), 1910-15 (Box 99, Folder 1741)
      - Checks (canceled), 1929-32 (Box 100, Folder 1742)
      - Checks (canceled), 1937 (Box 100, Folder 1743)
      - Checks (canceled), 1938 (Box 100, Folder 1744-1745)
      - Checks (canceled), 1939 (Box 100, Folder 1746-1747)
      - Checks (canceled), 1940 (Box 100, Folder 1748-1749)
      - Checks (canceled), 1941 (Box 101, Folder 1750-1751)
      - Checks (canceled), 1942 (Box 101, Folder 1752)
      - Checks (canceled), 1943 (Box 101, Folder 1753-1754)
      - Checks (canceled), 1944 (Box 101, Folder 1755)
      - Checks (canceled), 1945 (Box 101, Folder 1756)
      - Checks (canceled), 1946 (Box 102, Folder 1757)
      - Checks (canceled), 1954 (Box 102, Folder 1758)
    - Other Papers
      - Address book, 1920 (Box 102, Folder 1759)
      - Diary fragment, [1921?] Jan 25-26 (Box 102, Folder 1759a)
      - Notebooks, n.d. (Box 102, Folder 1760-1762)
      - Manuscript handled by Llewellyn Jones, entitled "The Wreath of Thorns", 1917 (Box 102, Folder 1763)
      - Pray & Sons vs. Llewellyn Jones, 1921-22
        See: Cases: Other Case Files, Box 64, folder 1225
      - Professional correspondence, 1918-27 (Box 102, Folder 1763a)
      - Tags and tickets, 1934-45, n.d. (Box 102, Folder 1763b)
      - Writings, 1899-1918 (Box 102, Folder 1764-1765)
      - Writings, n.d. (Box 103, Folder 1766-1770)
    - Printed Material
      - Newspaper article from society page, n.d. (Box 103, Folder 1771)
        Party at Mrs. Frank Lloyd Wright's house
      - College News Wellesley, Mass., 1909-11
        See: Oversize, Box 112, folders 1861-1866
      - Programs, handbooks, 1907-09 (Box 103, Folder 1772)
      - Programs, handbooks, 1915-51, n.d. (Box 103, Folder 1773)
      - Wellesley College programs and handbooks, 1912-13 (Box 103, Folder 1774)
      - Wellesley College programs and handbooks, 1932 (Box 103, Folder 1775)
    - Scrapbooks
      - Wellesley College, 1909-11 (Box 104, Folder 1776)
      - Wellesley College, 1911-13 (Box 105, Folder 1777)
      - Correspondence removed from scrapbook, 1909-10, n.d. (Box 106, Folder 1778)
      - Correspondence removed from scrapbook, 1911-12, n.d. (Box 106, Folder 1779-1782)
      - Correspondence removed from scrapbook, 1912-13, n.d. (Box 106, Folder 1783)
      - Christmas cards removed from scrapbook, 1911, n.d. (Box 106, Folder 1784-1786)
      - Miscellaneous items, 1910-13 (Box 106, Folder 1787)
        Found loose in scrapbook, unattached to any page
  - UNIDENTIFIED
    - Account book, 1883-85 (Box 107, Folder 1788)
      Entries are mostly names of Belvidere women
    - Diary used as account book?, [1884] (Box 107, Folder 1789)
      Most entries erased, now partially legible
    - Deed between Noah C. and Sarah S. Amsden and Houghton C. Walker, 1854 Aug 18
      See: Oversize, Box 112, folder 1867.
      There is a promissory note to Noah C. Amsden in George H. and Francis H. Rice's Bills and receipts. Otherwise the relationship to the Wilbur family is unknown
    - Bookmarks, n.d. (Box 107, Folder 1790)
    - Souvenir from Colorado Springs, Colorado, n.d. (Box 107, Folder 1791)
    - Writings, n.d. (Box 107, Folder 1792)
    - Research notes on Moses Cook, n.d. (Box 107, Folder 1792a)
- Printed Material, 1872-1929; Series V; 0.4; (1 box)
  Series IV, Printed Material, is organized into three subseries: Church Publications, Newspapers, and Miscellaneous.
  - CHURCH PUBLICATIONS
    - Manual of the First Presbyterian Church, 1917-29 (Box 108, Folder 1793)
    - Our Church Bell, 1898-1923 (Box 108, Folder 1794)
    - Miscellaneous pamphlets, 1876-1925, n.d. (Box 108, Folder 1795)
  - NEWSPAPERS
    - Belvidere Daily Republican, 1925 Sep 28
      See: Oversize, Box 113, folder 1870
    - Belvidere Standard, 1872-88
      See: Oversize, Box 113, folders 1871-1877
    - Daily News Extra Elgin, Illinois, [1881] Sep 20 (Box 108, Folder 1796)
    - Independent Belvidere papers, 1874-75 (Box 108, Folder 1797)
    - Oak Leaves Oak Park, Illinois, 1916 Oct 14 (Box 108, Folder 1798)
    - Pike's Peak Daily News, 1911 Jul 12
      See: Oversize, Box 113, folder 1878
  - MISCELLANEOUS
    - Advertisements, 1856, 1920, n.d. (Box 108, Folder 1799)
      See also: Oversize, Box 113, folder 1879
    - Advertising cards and booklets, 1874, 1909, n.d. (Box 108, Folder 1800)
    - Belvidere playbills and announcements, 1874, 1876 (Box 108, Folder 1801)
      See also: Oversize, Box 112, folder 1868
    - Calling cards--family, n.d. (Box 108, Folder 1802)
    - Calling cards--friends (Box 108, Folder 1803)
    - Calling cards--business, n.d. (Box 108, Folder 1804)
    - Engraving plate and cards for engagement announcement for Miss Mary Elizabeth Hicks and Doctor George Percy Brown (Box 108, Folder 1804a)
    - Northwestern University Bulletin, Vol. 22, no. 2, 1921 Jul 9 (Box 108, Folder 1804b)
    - Union College of Law. Closing examinations and graduation exercises. Offprint from Chicago Legal News, [1876] (Box 108, Folder 1804c)
    - Union Convention (broadside), 1873 (Box 108, Folder 1805)
- Photographs, 1872-1930; Series VI; 0.8; (2 boxes)
  Series V, Photographs, is organized into three subseries, Identified People, Unidentified People by Place, and Other Photographs.
  - IDENTIFIED PEOPLE
    - Wilbur Family
      - Wilbur, George W., [1880-86], n.d. (Box 109, Folder 1806)
      - Rice, Susan W., [1875-86] (Box 109, Folder 1807)
      - Wilbur, George R., [1890] (Box 109, Folder 1808)
      - Jones, Susan Wilbur, [1893-1901], n.d. (Box 109, Folder 1809-1810)
      - Wilbur, Helen, [1892-95] (Box 109, Folder 1811)
        Photographer: Hardy, Pomona, California
      - Jones, George and Llewellyn Jr., [1928-30] (Box 109, Folder 1812)
    - Others
      - Carleton, Ethel and Mary Trask (Box 109, Folder 1813)
      - Cook, Carrie, n.d. (Box 109, Folder 1814)
      - Cook, Chauncey S., n.d. (Box 109, Folder 1815)
      - Cook, Nelson, [1896] (Box 109, Folder 1816)
      - Gale, Fred C., n.d. (Box 109, Folder 1817)
  - UNIDENTIFIED PEOPLE BY PLACE
    - California
      - Pomona, n.d. (Box 109, Folder 1818)
        Photographer: Hardy, Octagon Gallery
      - San Francisco, [1900], n.d. (Box 109, Folder 1819)
        Photographers: B. F. Howland & Co., New York Photographic Gallery; Bradley & Rulofson; G. D. Morse; Ishiguro; John D. Godeus, South Park Photographic Gallery.
    - Canada
      - Montreal, n.d. (Box 109, Folder 1819a)
    - Illinois
      - Belvidere, [1872], n.d. (Box 109, Folder 1820-1822)
      - Bristol, n.d. (Box 109, Folder 1823)
      - Champaign, n.d. (Box 109, Folder 1824)
      - Chicago, n.d. (Box 109, Folder 1825)
      - Rockford, [1872] (Box 109, Folder 1826)
    - Kansas
      - Cheney, n.d. (Box 109, Folder 1827)
        Photographer: Oscar Sellon, Cheney, Kansas
    - Massachusetts
      - Lynn, [1882] (Box 109, Folder 1827a)
      - Pittsfield, n.d. (Box 109, Folder 1828)
    - Michigan
      - Ann Arbor, n.d. (Box 109, Folder 1829)
      - Chelsea, n.d. (Box 109, Folder 1830)
      - Miscellaneous, n.d. (Box 110, Folder 1831-1832)
    - New York
      - Syracuse, n.d. (Box 110, Folder 1833)
  - OTHER PHOTOGRAPHS
    - St. Louis Sampling & Testing Works, cyanotypes (2), n.d. (Box 110, Folder 1834)
    - Unidentified factory, cyanotypes (2), n.d. (Box 110, Folder 1835)
    - Unidentified people and artwork, cyanotypes (7) (Box 110, Folder 1835a)
    - Unidentified people, tintypes (7), n.d. (Box 110, Folder 1836)
    - Butler Hospital Adams Nervine, n.d. (Box 110, Folder 1837)
    - Miscellaneous, [1901], n.d. (Box 110, Folder 1838-1844)
- Oversize, 5; (3 boxes)
  Oversize contains oversize material from series II, III, IV, and V, and is listed in that order here.
  - GEORGE W. WILBUR'S PROFESSIONAL PAPERS
    - Cases: Long Term Individual Client Files
      - Burke, Robert L. and Michael
        - Official Map, North Half of the City of Miami Beach, Florida, 1925 (Box bsd, folder 1880)
    - Cases: Milling and Mining Files
      - Mining lease -- Louise and Moses Hawkes to Joel V. Taylor, 1885 Jun 2 (Box 112, Folder 1846)
      - Pittsburgh mine deed, 1889 Oct 22 (Box 112, Folder 1847)
      - Gurley, Charles D. vs. Ruby Chief Mining and Milling Company, Complaint, 1887 Mar 10 (Box 112, Folder 1848)
      - Mining lease (blank), n.d. (Box 112, Folder 1849)
      - Plat of Mines of Ruby Chief Mining and Milling Company (Box bsd, folder 1879a)
    - Correspondence
      - Letterpress book, 1879-84 (Box 111, Folder 1845)
  - GEORGE W. WILBUR'S PERSONAL AND PROFESSIONAL PAPERS
    - Business Records
      - Milling and Mining
        - Mining deed, n.d. (Box 112, Folder 1850)
        - Mining correspondence, 1896 Sep 17 (Box 112, Folder 1851)
        - Map of unidentified mine, n.d. (Box bsd, folder 1882)
        - Map of "Mammoth" mine, San Luis Obispo County, California, n.d. (Box 112, Folder 1852)
        - Map of "Mammoth" mine, San Luis Obispo County, California, n.d. (Box 113, Folder 1869)
    - Other Papers
      - George W. Wilbur's notary public commission, 1876 (Box 112, Folder 1853)
      - George W. Wilbur's diploma from Union College of Law, 1876 (Box 112, Folder 1854)
      - George W. Wilbur's license to practice law, 1876 (Box 112, Folder 1855)
      - Deed to George Wilbur from Michael and Mary Griffin of land in Chicago, 1882 Dec 28 (Box 112, Folder 1856)
  - OTHER FAMILY PAPERS
    - Cook and Rice Family Papers
      - Rice Family
        - Francis H. Rice and George H. Rice documents, 1859-60 (Box 112, Folder 1857-1858)
    - Wilbur, Ellen Rice
      - Printed Material
        - The Rockford Alumna Rockford College, 1932 Jan (Box 112, Folder 1859)
    - Jones, Susan Wilbur
      - Financial Papers
        - Apartment leases -- Llewellyn Jones, 1927-30 (Box 112, Folder 1860)
      - Printed Material
        - College News Wellesley, Mass., 1909-11 (Box 112, Folder 1861-1866)
    - Unidentified
      - Deed between Noah C. and Sarah S. Amsden and Houghton C. Walker, 1854 Aug 18 (Box 112, Folder 1867)
  - PRINTED MATERIAL
    - Newspapers
      - Belvidere Daily Republican, 1925 Sep 28 (Box 113, Folder 1870)
      - Belvidere Standard, 1872-88 (Box 113, Folder 1871-1877)
      - Pike's Peak Daily News, 1911 Jul 12 (Box 113, Folder 1878)
    - Miscellaneous
      - Advertisements
        - Mandel Brothers advertisements (Box 113, Folder 1879)
      - Belvidere playbills and announcements
        - The Conclave of the Trusty Five. A Tragedy in Two Parts., 1873 May 28 (Box 112, Folder 1868)
- Restricted Fragile Material, 2.7; (6 boxes)
  Restricted Fragile Papers contains fragile originals. The material is arranged in folder order and may only be seen with the permission of the appropriate curator.
  Conditions Governing Access
  Restricted fragile papers. Reference surrogates have been substituted in the main files. For further information consulte the appropriate curator.
  - Box 4, folder 68 (Box 114, Folder 1883)
  - Box 5, folders 77,86 (Box 114, Folder 1884)
  - Box 6, folder 102 (Box 114, Folder 1885)
  - Box 8, folder 138 (Box 114, Folder 1886)
  - Box 9, folders 162, 168, 171, 175, 177 (Box 114, Folder 1887)
  - Box 10, folder 184, 187, 194 (Box 114, Folder 1888)
  - Box 11, folder 236 (Box 114, Folder 1889)
  - Box 12, folder 251 (Box 114, Folder 1890)
  - Box 13, folders 269, 273, 275, 277, 278, 281 (Box 114, Folder 1891)
  - Box 14, folders 293-312 (Box 114, Folder 1892-1897)
  - Box 15, folders 313-318, 322, 329 (Box 114, Folder 1898-1899)
  - Box 16, folder 350 (Box 114, Folder 1899a)
  - Box 17, folders 362, 364-370, 373 (Box 114, Folder 1900-1902)
  - Box 18, folder 388, 393-394, 396, 399-402 (Box 114, Folder 1903-1906)
  - Box 21, folders 443-444, 446, 449, 452 (Box 114, Folder 1907)
  - Box 23, folders 501-503 (Box 114, Folder 1908-1909)
  - Box 24, folders 521, 523, 534 (Box 114, Folder 1910)
  - Box 25, folders 547-548, 553a (Box 114, Folder 1911-1912)
  - Box 25a, folder 560 (Box 114, Folder 1912a)
  - Box 26, folder 571 (Box 114, Folder 1913)
  - Box 38, folders 773-775 (Box 114, Folder 1914)
  - Box 39, folders 777-778, 783, 785 (Box 114, Folder 1915-1916)
  - Box 47, folders 893-895 (Box 114, Folder 1917-1918)
  - Box 63, folder 1187 (Box 114, Folder 1919)
  - Box 64, folder 1225 (Box 114, Folder 1920)